(Let it go.)
=Revenge From A Wife=
=Episode 7=
We've picked enough vine blossoms.
We're lucky to live in peaceful times.
So we can enjoy days like this.
Look at you.
We're here to relax. Why the long face?
Cheer up.
I made this herbal sachet earlier today.
The flowers are already inside.
Keep it by your pillow tonight.
You'll sleep well.
Does this herbal sachet
contain only vine blossoms?
No.
And I had a little motive of my own.
Vine blossoms have a cooling effect.
Your pulse suggests poor circulation.
I suspect your hands
and feet get cold at night.
So I added a few mild herbs.
The herbs may look a little dark,
but they're gentler than people.
If you still don't trust me, Mr. Gu,
leave the herbal sachet here.
I'll sell it to the next insomniac.
What if your herbal sachet works so well
I sleep soundly every night
and can't do without it?
Then I hope, Mr. Gu,
you'll sleep just as well
without the herbal sachet.
Today's consultation fee is
50 wen.
Call it a thank-you
for showing me this beautiful view.
May I ask
your name?
Su Cao.
Thank you, then.
I'll be going.
By the way, Mr. Gu.
Come back in two days for a follow-up.
Don't dwell on your worries before bed.
If you still can't sleep,
think of the peace we enjoy
and the beauty of these mountains.
I will.
Ms. Su.
(Everyone in the palace
who sees His Majesty)
(either fears him)
(or reveres him.)
(Only the Empress was different.)
(She'd have His Majesty)
(steady her ladder,)
(move flowers,)
(and grind ink for her.)
(She'd tease him about his handwriting)
(and call him clumsy.)
(Yet His Majesty loved it.)
(Because with the Empress,)
(he wasn't a ruler)
(or the emperor.)
(He was just a man)
(who wanted to be himself.)
(Your Majesty,)
(I'm a better replacement for
the late Empress than Consort Chen.)
(Are you satisfied?)
Your Majesty.
I haven't seen you these past two days.
Could it be...
I've done something wrong
and made you lose interest in me?
You're overthinking it.
I've just had
too much to do lately.
No matter how busy you are,
you still need to rest.
Your Majesty.
If you keep being so cold to me,
you'll hurt my feelings.
Your Majesty.
Do I
look pretty today?
Of course you do.
Then, Your Majesty...
look at me a little longer.
Oh!
Careful!
Mr. Gu.
Are you here for your follow-up?
There are quite a few people today.
So you may have to wait a little longer.
I'm free today.
I'll help.
All right.
Thank you, Mr. Gu.
This way.
I'll do it.
Oh.
Mr. Gu.
Keep an eye on the fire for me.
A headache.
A migraine?
Yes.
Mr. Gu.
This one?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you, miss.
Mr. Gu.
It'll be ready in a moment.
Here. This is for you.
Thank you!
♪Sunset fades beyond the lonely city♪
♪Dusk snow paints the green hills♪
♪A lone rider storms the old pass♪
♪Drunk, I gaze by lamplight♪
♪Old friends have all drifted away♪
♪My broken sword rusts, as do I♪
♪Jackdaws cry into the night♪
♪Half a banner snaps in the wind♪
♪In dreams, I return to the camps♪
♪Moonlight chills my armor♪
♪Life is a dream through many winters♪
♪I gaze beyond the edge of the world♪
♪Parting sorrow spills across the moon♪
♪The moon and wind mean nothing now♪
♪History turns to ash before ink dries♪
♪Who plays the zither
and sighs at the pavilion?♪
♪The past has faded away♪